Many people believe that working to the maximum is the secret to success, but research has found that moderation also gets results on the job.
许多人认为，拼尽全力工作是成功的秘诀，但研究发现，在工作中保持适度同样能取得成效。
In a study led by Ellen Langer of Harvard University, researchers asked people to translate sentences into a new made-up language.
在哈佛大学埃伦·兰格领导的一项研究中，研究人员让人们把句子翻译成一种新编出来的语言。
Subjects who practiced the language moderately beforehand made fewer errors than those who practiced extensively or not at all.
事先适度练习过这门语言的受试者，比大量练习或完全没练习的人犯错更少。
High levels of knowledge can make people too attached to traditional ways of viewing problems across fields: the arts, sciences, and politics.
无论是艺术、科学还是政治领域，知识水平高都可能使人过于执着于看待问题的传统方式。
High conscientiousness is related to lower job performance, especially in simple jobs where it doesn’t pay to be a perfectionist.
高度尽责与工作表现较差相关，在那些做完美主义者并不划算的简单工作中尤其如此。
How long we stay on the clock and how we spend that time are under careful examination in many workplaces.
我们在岗待多长时间、如何利用这段时间，在许多工作场所都受到仔细审视。
The young banker who eats lunch at his desk is probably seen as a go-getter, while his colleagues who chat over a relaxed conference-room meal get dirty looks from the corner office.
在办公桌前吃午饭的年轻银行职员很可能被看作积极进取的人，而他那些在会议室里悠闲地边吃边聊的同事，则会招来高层领导的白眼。
“People from cultures that value relationships more than ours does are shocked by the thought of eating alone in front of a computer,” says Art Markman, a professor of psychology at the University of Texas, Austin.
“有些文化比我们的文化更看重人际关系，来自这些文化的人一想到要独自对着电脑吃饭就会感到震惊，”得克萨斯大学奥斯汀分校心理学教授阿特·马克曼说。
Social interaction has been shown to lift mood and get people thinking in new directions and in ways that could help improve any post-lunch effort.
社交互动已被证明能提振情绪，让人们开始朝新的方向思考，而这样的思考方式可能有助于把午饭后的任何工作做得更好。
Markman also promotes off-task time.
马克曼也提倡留出脱离手头工作的时间。
“Part of being a good thinker is experiencing things that are seemingly unrelated to what you are working on at the moment but give you fresh ideas about your work,” he says.
“要做一个善于思考的人，有一点就在于去经历一些看似与你此刻手头的工作毫无关系、却能给你的工作带来新想法的事情，”他说。
“Also, there is a lot of research showing that a positive mood leads to higher levels of productivity and creativity.
“此外，大量研究表明，积极的情绪会带来更高的效率和创造力。
So, when people do things to increase their life satisfaction, they also make themselves more effective at work.”
所以，人们做一些事来提高自己的生活满意度时，也会让自己在工作中更有成效。”